stir food
grab kettle
open kettle
fill kettle
turn off tap
close kettle
put kettle
turn on kettle
open cowlid (?)
grab sauce pan
put saucepan
turn on hub
grab cup
put cup
turn on hub
open rice
pour rice
close rice
put rice
pour rice
put cup
grab salt
open salt
pour salt
put salt
shake saucer
open cupboard
grab lid
close cupboard
put lid
stir food
grab almond
open canned almonds
spoon
pour almonds
spoon almonds
close almonds
stir food
grab kettle
pour kettle
put lid
put kettle
stir food
grab almonds
pour almonds
stir food
Take out spoon
Tap spoon
Close almonds
Open cupboard
Put almonds
Close cupboard
Grab salt
Pour salt
Put salt
Stuff food
Rinse spoon
Spoon food
Stuff food
Put spatula
Turn down heat
Put spoon
Pick up glass
Put glass
Turn down hob
[END SUBTITLE]